fullyfreedown.com 2012-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Bollywood Songs

### **Privacy Statement for FullyFreeDown.com**

FullyFreeDown.com Limited (“www.FullyFreeDown.com”) owns or controls, and provides access to the FullyFreeDown.com website, currently located at http://www. FullyFreeDown.com (the “Website”).

### **Browser Information**

We collect data regarding the users of FullyFreeDown.com, including: (i) The Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user’s computer. This may or may not be associated with a particular Internet Service Provider (ISP); (ii) The referring URL, if any; (iii) The browser software identification (i.e. the brand and version of your browser software).

### **Statistical Information**

We log certain information concerning the listening, skipping and music-sharing activities of users and other activities whilst they use the Website, and we may match such information with personally identifiable information concerning such users. For example, it is possible for us to know which records you listen to, which you skip, which you recommend to other users and which you add to your record collection. However, information related to your listening, skipping and music-sharing activities may be viewed by all other users in conjunction with your FullyFreeDown.com username and by third parties who have access to this information via FullyFreeDown.com’s API and webservices, as further explained in this Policy.

Please note that we do log and use statistical information in the aggregate. For example, we know the number of users who skip a particular song. From this information we are able to compile statistics in the form of percentages of all users (i.e. 29% of our users skipped song XYZ). We can of course compare the skipping statistics of one song to those of another song. We are also able to perform more sophisticated statistical operations based on the information collected. For example, we can determine the raw number (and associated percentages) of users who listen to one particular song that also listen to other particular songs. From this information, we are able to determine which songs are “neighbours” in terms of overall listener taste and we can see which genres of music tend to be neighbours. As a service, we may supply certain aggregate statistical information to record labels and artists that allow us to stream their music on FullyFreeDown.com in order to help them understand the likes and dislikes of music listeners.

### **Third Party Cookies**

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

We may display links to third party sites. However, we cannot control and cannot be held responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. We advise you to check their terms of use and privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

We use cookies to help you use FullyFreeDown.com to collect data that we can use to improve the efficiency and quality of our service. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid user and to help personalize your FullyFreeDown experience in conjunction with your profile. We currently employ persistent cookies which stay on your computer after you have gone offline. Persistent cookies remain in the “cookies” folder after you have closed your web browser.

Most browsers have cookies turned on as a default, but you can always disable cookies or only allow non-persistent cookies via your browser preferences. If you choose to disable cookies, however, you won’t be able enjoy a significant proportion of FullyFreeDown.com functionality. Please remember that cookies cannot read your hard drive or give any information collected to any third party. A cookie can only be read by the organization that sets it.

### **External Links**

FullyFreeDown.com contains links of other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites we link to. We do make an effort to avoid linking to known “adult” and “porn” sites. FullyFreeDown.com is a family web site.

### **Changes Our Privacy Policy**

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site.

If you decide that you do not want your personal information to be used in the way described in this Policy, you can send us a notice that you wish to withdraw your consent as set out above by emailing [anisur96@gmail.com](mailto:anisur96@gmail.com) . Because the FullyFreeDown community relies on users sharing information, withdrawing your consent will mean that you are not able to receive the full benefits of FullyFreeDown.com service as a user. Additionally, if you do not provide your consent, or if you withdraw your consent, you should not use the Website as a registered user, which means that many features will be unavailable to you.

### **Legally-Compelled Disclosures**

We believe in privacy and therefore will take all reasonable measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information remains private. However, in the event that we are required to disclose personally identifiable information by a court, the police or other law enforcement bodies for their investigations, regulation or other governmental authority we will make such a disclosure without being in violation of this Policy.
